I met a traveler from an antique land
who said,
"Two vast and trunkless legs of stone
stand in the desert.
Near them, on the sand, half sunk, a
shattered visage lies, whose frown and
wrinkled lip and sneer of cold command
tell that its sculptor well those
passions read which yet survive, stamped
on these lifeless things.
The hand that mocked them and the heart
that fed.
And on the pedestal these words appear:
'My name is Ozymandias, King of Kings.
Look on my works, ye mighty, and
despair!'"
Nothing beside [clears throat] remains.
Round the decay of that colossal wreck,
boundless and bare, the lone and level
sands
stretch far away.
>> [music]